It's Shi-chan, right?
シーちゃんだよね?
that's right.
そうです
This is Ishikawa.
石川です
Thank you very much.
ありがいまして
That's still the case.
それまんまだね
It's cute just like that.
そのまんま、かわいいって
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Well then, it's cute.
じゃあ、かわいいね
I've been standing here for a very long time.
ここに立ってるのすごい長いから
It's a bit cold.
ちょっと寒いね
It's cold, isn't it?
寒いですよね
Isn't it cold?
寒くない?
It's cold.
寒いですよ
I've failed a bit so far.
こっちまでちょっと失敗しちゃったね
It's a little thin.
ちょっと薄いです
I didn't think it would be this cold.
こんな寒いと思わなくて
Wow, that's cute.
すごい、かわいいね
It looks a little like JC.
なんかちょっとJCにも見えちゃうね
is that so?
そうですか?
Don't you say I'm too young?
幼いって言われない?
There's a video, right?
動画あるんだよね
What do you usually do?
いつも何してるの?
everytime?
いつも?
Yeah.
うん
I'm always at home.
いつもでも家にいるんだ
I'm at home.
家にいるんだ
I see.
そっか
After a long time.
久々に
I agree.
そうだね
I have come to this place.
こういうとこ来ました
I agree.
そうだね
Since when have people stopped visiting zoos?
動物園っていうのはいつから来てない?
It was in middle school or something.
中学とかでしたね
Ever since I went there for a school event.
学 校の行事で行って以来
That's right.
そうなんだ
I may not have gone.
行ってないかもしれないです
I don't have many opportunities to go there.
結構行く機会がなくないです
I agree.
そうだね
Isn't something going to happen when you grow up?
大人になったら何かあるんじゃない?
What's going on?
何だかんだ
On a date or something.
デートとかで
Yes, on a date.
そう、デートとかで
I see.
なるほど
It doesn't have legs yet.
まだ足がないからね
It's been a long time since I've been here.
久々に来ました
Tiger and...
虎と...
I don't understand anything.
何か分かんないで
Then it's a tiger.
じゃあ虎です
What comes first?
何が最初にあるんですかね?
At first it was just birds.
最初は鳥ばっかだね
Something like a flying squirrel.
ムササビとか
I watched this in order.
順番にこうやって見ました
It looks good after all.
やっぱり映りいいね
As expected.
さすがだね
It looks great, really.
映りいいよ、めっちゃ
It's cute though.
かわいいんだけど
cute.
かわいい
It's definitely fine, I think she'll become an idol.
絶対いいよ、アイドルになると思うんだよな
Is that your approach?
そういうアプローチとかしてるの?
I don't know if he's riding.
乗ってるか分かんなくて
Ah, I don't know yet.
あ、まだ分かんないんだ
That's right.
そうね
It's got my face on it quite a bit.
結構自分のお顔乗ってるじゃん
I feel like I'm working a little hard on SNS.
SNSをちょっと頑張ってるって感じ
There are a lot of suspicious people here, so be careful.
なんか怪しい人いっぱいだから気をつけてね
got it.
わかりました
I think it will definitely sell.
絶対売れると思うんだけど
Ah, there you are.
あ、いますね
What is this?
なんだろこれ?
Donkey.
ロバ
goat?
ヤギ?
A goat?
ヤギか
It's a goat.
ヤギだ
It says Bock.
ボックって書いてあるね
Wow, that's cute.
え、かわいいですね
He said it was nice and cute.
良かった、かわいいって言ってくれた
It's quiet.
静かで
静かだね
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
あ、あ、あ、あ、あ
It's sitting.
座ってるじゃん
Would you like to go nearby?
近くに行ってみない?
He's quiet, isn't he?
大人しいんですね
But a goat?
でも ヤギ?
Don't touch the goat.
ヤギに触らない
It's true, it's a goat.
本当だね、ヤギだ
It's a goat, a goat.
ヤギですね、ヤギ
Texture, angularity, whelk, firmness.
キメ、アン、ツブ、コシ
I wonder if he's replying to me?
返事してくれてるのかな?
But I turned this way.
でもこっち向いたよ
That's good.
よかったじゃん
You're saying something, okay?
何か言ってますね、じゃあ
I'm angry, I'm angry.
怒ってる、怒ってる
I'm being intimidated.
威嚇されてるよ
Are you angry?
怒ってる?
Because I'm a little angry.
ちょっと怒ってるから
Wow, there's a rabbit.
すごい、ウサギがいる
Japanese rabbit.
日本のウサギ
which one?
どれ?
Is this it?
これか
I have long legs.
足長いんですよ
Are you doing it?
してるの?
I wonder if I can stand now.
立たないかな、今
this?
これ?
I don't know what to do.
足分かんないね
It looks kind of short though.
なんか短く見えるけど
I'm sitting down now.
今座っちゃってる
cute.
かわいい
I was able to see a rabbit, so I'm a little satisfied.
ウサギ見れたんで、ちょっと満足します
Don't say you're going home.
もう帰るとか言わないでよ
It's still deeper.
まだもっと奥にいますよ
It's already winter.
もう 冬ですね
It goes by so quickly, isn't it?
あっという間ですよね
That's terrible.
やばいね
Were you at home the whole time?
ずっとお家にいたの?
1 year.
1年間
I'm going to school.
学校行ってますよ
If you feel like it.
気がついたらね
It seems like it was winter.
冬だったみたいな
I actually go to school.
本当 に学校行ってますよ
Are you improving yourself to become an idol?
アイドルになるために自分磨いたりしてるの?
Are you singing or not dancing?
ダンスなしとか歌ったりとかしてるの?
Haven't done anything yet?
まだ何もしてない?
I'm not doing anything.
何もしてないです
Take care of your body shape.
体型気をつけようって
Are you careful about what you eat?
食べ物気をつかってんの?
Yes, I'm careful.
うん、気をつかってます
Looks like you've discovered something.
何か発見したみたいね
Did you say something?
何か言った?
Wow.
うわ ー
what?
何?
I said it was amazing.
すごいって言った
amazing.
すごい
It's huge.
でかいね
The corners are amazing.
角がすごい
Because it's Shui beef.
シュイ牛だから
Shui beef.
シュイ牛だね
シュイ牛
It's a cow.
シ ュ イ 牛 だ ね
I like the elephant.
ゾウさんがいいよ
It's true.
本当だ
It's huge.
でかいね
Which is better, Shui Beef?
シュイ牛とどっちがいい?
Elephants are better.
ゾウの方がいいね
Elephants are more docile.
ゾウの方がおとなしいよね
cute.
かわいい
I saw this.
こっち見た
It's Dumbo.
ダンボだよ
It's true.
ほんとだ
It's a tiger.
トラだ
Won't you take a closer look?
近くで見ない?
scared?
怖い?
But it's quiet.
でも、おとなしいよ
Because I didn't say anything.
何も言ってないから
It's come, it's come.
来 た来た
cute.
かわいい
Looks like a cat.
猫ちゃんみたい
big cat
大きい猫ちゃん
Aren't you scared?
怖くないんですか?
cute.
かわいい
amazing.
すごい
near.
近く
Won't you run away?
逃げないかな?
Will I run away?
逃げるかな?
hey hey.
おいおい
Do you eat here?
ここで食べるの?
ここ で食べるの?
Let me see.
見 せてくれ
service station.
サービステーション
I'm eating.
食べてる
Can't you hear the mystery?
謎聞こえない?
Try hiding it.
隠してみて
Bring it here.
ここに持ってきて
It's cute.
かわいいですね
I'm looking at you and eating.
こっち見て食べてる
It caught my attention.
気になれたね
He's a good boy.
いい子ですね
amazing.
すごい
It's cold everyone.
みんな寒いからね
Everyone was curled up.
みんな丸まってた
Is it cold?
寒いんですかね?
You're close to me.
寄り添ってるね
I agree.
そうだね
It won't let me down.
落ち込めてくれないです
That kid seems depressed.
あの子落ち込んでるっぽい
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
Pochin alone.
一人でポチンと
I'm depressed.
落ち込んでる
It's a bit like blue.
ちょっとブルーみたいな
yes?
はい?
Chigoi?
ちごい?
Is it small?
ちごいの?
You're making fun of me.
馬鹿にしてる
I don't know.
知らないよ
Ah, that's cute.
あ、かわいい
That's amazing.
すごいね
Really.
本当に
Feels cute.
かわいい感じ
Please stop.
やめてください
I'm making fun of you.
馬鹿にしてますよ
cute.
かわいい
I'm excited today.
きょうちテンション上がったね
I was more excited than the rabbit.
ウサギよりテンション上がった
surely.
確かに
It was going up.
上がってた
What do you want next?
次何みたい?
Second-rate?
次?
Raccoons, Leicester pandas, etc.
あらいぐまとかレスターパンダとか、
I want to see this area.
この辺見たいです
Leicester panda.
レスターパンダね
What's that instead of a Leicester panda?
レスターパンダじゃなくて何だっけ?
What did you want to see?
何見たいっつったっけ?
raccoon.
あらいぐま
Raccoon.
あらいぐまね
Aren't there similarities between a raccoon and a Leicester panda?
あ らいぐまとレスターパンダって何か似てない?
I don't know?
分からない?
I like that it's quiet.
静かなのがいいね
It's quiet.
静かだね
Isn't Kowara the quietest?
こわら一番静かなんじゃない?
Everyone was pretty quiet.
結構みんな静かでしたよね
I did it again.
またしました
This is Leicester Panda.
レスターパンダです
The one I saw the most.
一番見たやつで
It's over there.
あそこにいるよ
The Leicester panda may be the cutest.
や っぱレスターパンダが一番かわいいかもしれない
TRUE?
本当?
cute.
かわいい
I want you to come closer.
もっと近く来てほしいよね
But I'm eating it.
でも食べてますね
I kind of screamed.
なんか叫んだな
It might be from here.
こっちからかもしれない
cute.
かわいい
Ah, I'm gone.
あ、行っちゃった
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
disappointing.
残念
I just came here.
ちょっと来ましたね
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけね
Do you have something to write down?
何か念書く?
I came all the way.
せっかく来た
For memories.
思 い出に
Was it something cute?
何か可愛かった?
Leicester panda was cute.
レスターパンダ可愛かった
The koala was also the best.
コアラもさっき一番良かったじゃん
But Lester's panda was cuter.
でもレスターパンダのほうが可愛かった
So now Leicester's panda and koala.
じゃあ今のレスターパンダと コアラ
It might be a little troublesome.
ちょっと悩むかもしれないですね
Shall I buy you two then?
じゃあ2つ買ってあげようか
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
Instead, I was interested in that place.
その代わりさ、 あそこ、あれ気になっちゃった
Could you please show your face in the photo?
写真で顔を立ててくれない?
If you show me that, I'll buy it.
それを見せてくれたら買ってあげる
Two?
2つですか?
Yes, two.
そう、2つ
This one should be bigger.
こ っちが大きいほうがいい
Place the object properly and do it with both hands.
ちゃんとそれを物を置いて 両手でしてね
yes.
はい
Ah, so cute.
あ、可愛い
cute.
可愛い
Did you say face?
顔って言った?
You didn't say face.
顔って言ってないんですね
face.
顔
Yes, thank you.
はい、ありがとう
I'll buy it for you.
買ってあげる
It was so cute.
めっちゃ可愛かった
It was cute.
可愛かった
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Was it a raccoon dog and a monkey?
タヌキとサルだったっけ?
No.
違います
Leicester panda and koala.
レスターパンダとコアラ
Leicester panda koala.
レスターパンダのコアラね
Look.
見て
Do you have it?
ありますかね?
I wonder if there is?
あるんじゃないかな?
It's small.
ちっちゃいね
There's a lot over there.
あっちにいっぱいあるわ
It's true.
本当だ
Core opened.
コア開いた
cute.
可愛い
The middle one is the cutest though.
真ん中が一番可愛いけど
cute.
可愛い
thank you.
ありがとう
This is cute too.
これ も可愛いじゃん
Because I'm eating.
食べてるから
I also eat sweets.
お菓子も食べます
Let's eat together.
一緒に食べような
together.
一 緒に
It's cute.
可愛いね
Assortment of sweets.
お菓子詰め合わせ
Maybe biscuits?
ビスケットとかかな?
I wonder what it is.
なんだ ろうね
Instead, I came here.
それより、ここに来ちゃったね
I feel like it's here.
来ちゃったねって感じなんだけど
This is cute too.
これも可愛い
Ah, this is cute.
あ、これが可愛い
eat?
食べる?
Can I eat it?
食べていい?
I'll eat it later.
あとで食べる
It's cute.
可愛いね
可愛いですね
It was fun.
楽しかったね
However, he doesn't seem to remember a single sentence about this room.
でも、ここの部屋が 一文が覚えていないそう
Here we are.
ここにいるのは
first time?
初めて?
It's spacious.
広いよね
Isn't it beautiful?
綺麗じゃない?
It's beautiful.
綺麗ね
Mom and dad, are you sleeping like this?
お父さんとお母さん、こういうの寝てるの?
double bed.
ダブルベッド
separately?
別々?
Do you have a bed like this at home?
お家にこういうベッドある?
A wide one.
広いやつ
Are you going to sleep alone?
一人で寝ちゃうの?
That's right, it's lonely.
そうなんだ、寂しいね
Can I touch you?
触っていいの?
I'm touching it though.
触っちゃってるけども
Did you see it?
見えた?
見えちゃった?
Is it moist?
しっとりしてる?
I don't think so.
い かないね
cute.
可愛い
You want to be an idol, right?
アイドルになりたいんだよね
That's fine.
いいじゃん
She looks like an idol already.
すでにアイドルみたい
Do you have any special skills?
得意技とかあるの?
what?
何ですか?
Proud skill?
得意技?
No.
ダメです
What if I make a final pose?
決 めポーズにしたら?
why?
なんで?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいですよ
It's cute.
可愛いじゃん
Jewel idol.
宝珠アイドル
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
what happened?
どうしたの?
What did you just do?
今何したの?
What did you do?
何したの?
What happened?
何が起きたの?
Chew.
チュー
I chewed it.
チューしちゃった
Want a deeper chew?
もっとディープなチューする?
Can you show me?
見せてくれる?
Highest.
最高
I've been standing up.
立ってきた
Open your legs.
足開いて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Embarrassment that hit my face.
顔を届いた恥ずかしい
This one is more embarrassing.
こっちの方が恥ずかしい
Is this embarrassing?
こ っちが恥ずかしい?
What if I open my legs again?
もう一回足開いたら?
The blur is transparent.
ブラー透けてる
pink blur.
ピンクのブラー
Could you please just remove this button?
このボタンだけ外してくれる?
pink.
ピンク
Show me well.
よく見せて
Can I see Chikubi too?
チクビも見ていい?
Can I watch Newlin and Chikubi?
ニューリンとチクビ見ていいですか?
Can you show me something?
何か見せてくれる?
It's got a huge stain.
すごいシミになってる
It's stained.
シ ミになってる
Can you see it?
見られる?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
amazing.
すごい
Naughty.
エッチ
It's stained.
シミになってる
amazing.
すごい
It's getting really big.
めっちゃ大きくなってる
Have you ever touched your father?
お父さん触ったことあるよね?
The feeling of moving it up and down like this.
こうやって上下に動かす気持ち
Did you occasionally touch her like this by chance?
たまにこうやって、たまたまとか触ったんですか?
Do you want to check this out?
こっちへ調べてみる?
He looks great.
すごい格好してる
Should I face you?
向 かいでこっち向ける?
向かいでこっち向ける?
Did you know it came out?
出たの分かった?
Toktoku.
トクトクって
Do you understand?
分かるの?
Inside.
中で
That's a really good complaint.
すごい良いお文句だからね
It won't come out.
出てこないね
It's kind of surreal.
なんかシュールだね
Do you know anything?
何か分かる?
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
It's a heart.
ハートだよ
Try touching it.
触ってみて
Looks classy, ​​right?
高級そうでしょ?
Lean on it.
持たれかかって
Shall I take off my skirt?
スカート脱いちゃう?
Can you take off your skirt?
ス カート脱いでくれる?
It's not dirty, it's your skirt.
汚してないよね、スカートね
It's okay.
大丈夫だね
Take off your vest too.
チョッキも脱いで
What do you mean?
なんていうの?
Isn't that a vest?
チョッキじゃないの?
that.
それ
What do you mean?
なんていうの?
sweater.
セーター
It's called a sweater.
セーターって言うんだ
not go.
いかない
It's a waistcoat.
チ ョッキよ
Open your legs.
足開いて
You're a little shy.
ちょっと恥ずかしがってるね
Don't hide it, put it in.
隠せず入れて
Put it in yourself like this.
自分にこうやって入れて
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Look at me.
映ってよ
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Once I calmed down, I couldn't spread it out like this.
落ち着いたらこうやって広げられなかった
It would be embarrassing if it didn't make it to Mank.
マンクに上げられなかったら恥ずかしい
Both are embarrassing.
どっちも恥ずかしい
This makes me laugh.
ブルブルするね、これ
Lend me your finger.
指貸して
copper?
どう?
want?
欲しい?
Is it okay to be in the most sensitive area?
一番敏感なところでいてもいい?
First pleasure?
初めての快感?
Wow, I'm getting wet.
すごい、濡れてきちゃった
A lot of juice is coming out from inside.
中から汁がいっぱい出てきてるよ
Have you ever done anything yourself?
自分でも何とかしたことあるの?
what?
何?
I don't know if you went there, I'm sure.
行ったとか分かんないよね、きっと
Have you ever been there?
行 ったことある?
Look at this.
見て、これ
It's really shaped here.
めっちゃ形してる、ここ
This is what happened.
これがあってたのなんだね
You can feel the vibration in your hand as well.
持ってる手にも振動がすごい伝わってくる
It's getting wetter and wetter.
どんどん濡れてきてる
The camera is getting really wet.
すっごい濡れてきてる、カメラ
air
気
It lasts a long time.
持 ちいい
I feel like I'm trembling.
ブルブルする、なんか
Wow, this looks like I'm going to open it.
すごい、開けちゃいそうだね、これ
This has strong vibrations.
振動強いね、これ
It’s your first time, right?
初めての感触でしょ?
How do you feel?
どんな気分?
Is there something different from before?
さっきとなんか違う?
Do you have the same feeling?
同じ感じがついてる?
I'll take it out.
抜いてあげる
Is it like this?
こうかな?
It's done, it's done.
できた、できた
I'm getting really wet.
めっちゃ濡れてきちゃったよ
It was really wet.
めっちゃ濡れたね
Let's try it again.
もう一回やってしよう
Stick your butt out.
お尻を突き出してよ
Will you take my turn to lick me?
順番になって舐めてくれる?
Come.
来て
Sound of footsteps.
足音して
Which one about Gaos?
ガオスのところどっちがよ?
Can't support it?
支えられない?
Can you move it yourself like this?
こうやって自分で動かせる?
It's so hot, inside.
ピチャピチャだね、中ね
I'm so wet.
めっちゃ濡れてる
The coat came out fine.
コートちゃんと出てきたわ
I wish I could be told that I can cum inside you.
中出していいよって言われたらいいんだけど
Is it okay?
大丈夫かな?
I put it out twice though.
2回も出しちゃったけど